personalfn.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy

Maintaining the privacy of user’s information is important to us. This privacy statement outlines how we collect information from you, when you register as a user at www.PersonalFN.com (site or website) or when you subscribe to our online services and what we do with that information.

When you browse through the pages of the website, read or download information, we may collect, note or analyze details about your visit such as:

  * Your server address
  * Your operating system, top level domain name and the type of web browser you use
  * The date and time of your visit to the website
  * Whether you have visited the website previously
  * What pages of the website you accessed and what you downloaded
  * Your usage pattern and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of various areas of the site.

The information we collect relates to your server or PC rather than yourself.

The information we collect will be used within Quantum Information Services P Ltd or its website www.PersonalFN.com (PersonalFN) to help us improve our online services keeping in mind your needs, and to help us to provide you faster navigation and access to the various sections of the website. We may disclose this information to other persons for these purposes or for related purposes, including to information technology companies who assist us in constructing, designing and maintaining the website.

We will also collect your personal details while registering you as a user or subscriber of our various online services, or when you wish to download certain documents from our website or if you email us with a comment or query. We will use your details:

  * To send you the documents you have ordered
  * To answer your comment or query
  * To monitor our responses to you
  * For our internal sales and marketing analysis

We may also contact you to follow up on your order or request, or to provide you with further information about our products and services which may be of interest to you. Where we need to send you any documents, we may disclose your personal details to the mailing houses, printers or document management providers which PersonalFN uses so that they can forward the documents to you on our behalf.

We may share information we collect via the website to other members of the Quantum Group who may use the same to provide you with information on various products and services which may be of interest to you.

If you want to find out what personal information (if any) we hold in respect of you which has been collected through the website, or if you wish to update or correct your personal information, please contact us.

### Collection of information

The user represents that he is fully aware that in the course of using this website or in the process of subscribing to the products and services or part of it, PersonalFN may obtain information relating to the user, including that of a confidential nature. PersonalFN does not collect personal information about the user except when such users specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such information may be collected through the registration process for subscribing to services and in connection with contest submission, message boards, suggestions & votings/ polling activities. This information will be used by PersonalFN for its internal purposes and will be kept confidential. Personal information on users will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user. 

### Privacy commitments

PersonalFN is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its users and has taken all necessary and reasonable measures to protect the confidentiality of the users information and its transmission through the world wide web and it shall not be held liable for disclosure of the confidential information when in accordance with this Privacy Commitment or in terms of the agreements, if any, with the users. Employees of PersonalFN will not discuss the business affairs of any user with any other employee, except on a strict need-to-know basis.

### Use of Information

PersonalFN undertakes not to disclose the information provided by the users to any person, unless such action is necessary to:

  * Conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process such as requests of the government, court, tribunal, authority or other regulatory agency and/or required by any law;
  * Protect and defend PersonalFN’s or its Affiliates' rights, interests or property;
  * Enforce the terms and conditions under which its products and/or services are sold; or
  * Act to protect the interests of PersonalFN, its Affiliates, or its members, constituents or of other persons.

PersonalFN may use and/ or share the information provided by the users as it may deem necessary with its Affiliates and third parties for providing services and any service-related activities in order to serve you better. In this regard it may be necessary to disclose the user information to one or more agents and contractors of PersonalFN, and their sub-agents or sub-contractors, but such agents, sub-agents, contractors and sub- contractors will be required to use such information only for the stipulated services.

PersonalFN may disclose the user’s personal information to government, court, tribunals, authorities or other regulatory agency and/ or as may be required by the law to comply with their bonafide request. In either case PersonalFN shall be bound by and shall at all times have the legal right to disclose any or all personal information given by the user to it and PersonalFN shall not be held responsible or liable for any eventuality, loss or damage to the user that may arise out of such action on its part.

Further, some of the user information is maintained in PersonalFN's marketing database. PersonalFN may contact a user either by post, or by telephone or e-mail primarily as a follow-up to the user's request/enquiry or to answer any questions. PersonalFN may also contact a user from time to time in respect of other products and services that may be of interest to users. If a user does not wish to receive information about these products or services, the user may simply contact PersonalFN by phone, e-mail or post and communicate its desire not to receive information on these products or services.

PersonalFN may inform advertisers of information on user’s behavior and characteristics showing interest in various areas of the PersonalFN website as well as number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banner. PersonalFN will provide only aggregate data from such analysis done by it to third parties. Also, users should be aware that PersonalFN may sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through PersonalFN. PersonalFN is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and users should check the applicable privacy policy of such party when providing personally identifiable information.

### Opt-Out

If, at any time after registering for information or subscribing to any of our services, you wish to discontinue receiving information from us or you wish to opt out of our marketing or promotional emails, phone calls or discontinue receiving any other direct communication from us, please either click on the "unsubscribe" link available in the service/promotional/marketing emails or send us your request to unsubscribe at info@PersonalFN.com

### Policy against advertising PersonalFN website using unsolicited email messages

PersonalFN ensures that all emails promoting www.Personalfn.com or its services or the domains owned by it are sent only to subscribers who have agreed to receive such messages. PersonalFN prohibits any advertising of its brand and Website using unsolicited email messages. Any non compliance with this policy would cause partnership termination and/or affiliate account termination.

If you feel that you have received unsolicited emails from PersonalFN and would like to register a compliant, please contact us at info@PersonalFN.com We will on a best effort basis investigate all complaints related to unsolicited email messages.

### Security

The user shall cooperate with PersonalFN in order to ensure the security of the information, and we recommend that the users necessarily choose their passwords carefully such that no unauthorized access is made by a third party. The users should undertake not to disclose their password to anyone or keep any written or other record of the password such that a third party could access it.

### Payment through credit card

In case of subscription to services through online card payments, PersonalFN may obtain private information from the Subscriber including but not limited to date of birth, card number, card expiry date and such other details as may be required by the online payment gateway or as required under any law for the time being in force. 

In such cases, PersonalFN shall take all measures including following such security practices and procedures designed to protect all private information obtained from the Subscriber from unauthorised access, damage, use, modification, disclosure or impairment, as may be deemed necessary and reasonable or as may specified by any law for the time being in force.

### Cookies 

Users are also aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of PersonalFN's internet servers or through the use of "cookies." "Cookies" are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising

Cookies are not programs that come onto a user's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. Users are also hereby being made aware that PersonalFN cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for PersonalFN. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, users should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available from PersonalFN.

PersonalFN reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

### Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Please note that this Privacy Statement does not extend to third party sites linked to this website.

Amendments

PersonalFN reserves the right to modify the whole or some sections of this Privacy Statement at any time. Please check this statement from time to time for any changes.

### Amendments 

PersonalFN reserves the right to modify the whole or some sections of this Privacy Statement at any time. Please check this statement from time to time for any changes.

References

  * to 'you, 'your' and yours' are references to the person(s) accessing this website.
  * to 'we', 'us' and 'our' are references to mean individually and collectively, Quantum, PersonalFN & its directors, officers and employees.
